Mohammad Elias Hamidi

sex: Male / Date of Birth: 26-05-2000

+93 767280458 eliashamidi8@gmail.com Ahmad Shah Baba Mena, 12th District, Kabul-Afghanistan

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science and Technology from Shenyang University of Chemical Technology China with more than two years of experience as IT Assistant and Lecturer at private Universities. I possess experience with Programming Languages, Network, Data Analysis, Kobo Toolkit, SurveyCTO, Data Management & Database.

Professional Experience -

Ulearna Learning Center - Kabul

AUG-2023 - Current

Technology Content Creator

- · Part Time
- Content Creator: Recording Technology Content for online publication. My first online course of Python Programming published successfully.
- Smooth Performance Adviser: Providing Support as an adviser in order to improve the content quality.

Jahan University - Kabul

Lecturer

FEB 2023 - AUG 2023

- Responsible for teaching C++ programming language & Database subjects.
- · Content Quality Adviser
- · Seminars Provider in advance technology

Dunya University - Kabul Lecturer

MAR 2023 - JUN 2023

- Part Time
- Responsible for teaching Python programming language.
- · Content Quality Adviser

Organization for Development and Sustainable Services in Afghanistan (ODSSA) - Kabul IT Assistant

MAR 2017 - JAN 2018

- Installed and configured software and hardware
- Monitored system performance to identify potential issues.
- Researched and identified solutions to technical problems.
- Assisted in development of system security protocols.
- Configured hardware, devices, and software to set up work stations for employees.
- · Providing Data analysis services
- · Adviser for Data Collection and quality improvement
- Supervising Fresh Employees

Education

Bachelor o	f Computer	Science &	Tecl	hnol	ogy
------------	------------	-----------	------	------	-----

2023

Shenyang University of Chemical Technology - CHINA

Distinction: With Distinction

High School

2018

Ghulam Sediq Muhibi High School - CKABUL

English Language Diploma

2018

Muslim English Language Institute - Kabul

Key Skills

Data Management and Storage

Programming Languages (Python, Front-End,)

MS Office Suite **Data Analysis**

Kobo ToolKit

Operations Support Excellent Communication Analytical Abilities

Data Entry SurveyCTO Familiar with Productive AI tools, cloud based services and Apps

Time Management Information Security Advisor

Languages

ΙT



Workshops & Seminars

· Hack & Information Security

2023

Afghanistan Seminars Center CERTIFICATE OF PARTICIPATION

Volunteer Work

- Student Advisor and event organizer (2020,2023), International students Union, Shenyang University of Chemical Technology - CHINA
- Volunteer in Summer Camp (2020, 2023) Shenyang University of Chemical Technology CHINA
- Volunteer Assistant for controlling students during COVID-19 Shenyang University of Chemical Technology - CHINA

Interests

When I am not working, I enjoy taking walks, spending time with my family and watching movies. I am also a passionate reader of non-fiction & fiction books.